A Guide to the John D. Rockefeller, Sr. papers FA002
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Financial materials, 1800-1915; F
  - Charities Index Cards, 1863-1903; FV14
    - Hyde Park Baptist Church (Chicago, Illinois) - $3,442.00, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 721)
      Waite, R. N.
    - India Famine Relief Fund - $5,000.00, 1900 (Box 4, Folder 722)
      Brown Brothers
    - Indiana Monetary Conference - $1,000.00, 1897-1899 (Box 4, Folder 723)
      Mitchell, John J.; Strong, Hon. W. L.
    - Industrial Christian Alliance - $450.00, 1895-1900 (Box 4, Folder 724)
      Beemer, James G.; Bryant, R.; Townsend, John P.
    - Industrial Colony Association (Gardiner, New York) - $350.00, 1898-1899 (Box 4, Folder 725)
      Caldwell, Carrie; Fuess, Frederick W.
    - Industrial Education Association (New York College for Training Teachers) - $10,885.00, 1885-1891 (Box 4, Folder 726)
      Bussing, J. S.; Dodge, Miss Grace H.; Prof. Seward; Villard, H.
    - Industrial Exhibition - $20.00, 1886 (Box 4, Folder 727)
      Rickoff, Mrs. A. J.
    - Industrial School (Cleveland, Ohio; also called Children's Aid Society) - $7,260.28, 1864-1902 (Box 4, Folder 728)
      Mather, Samuel; Rev. Sampson; Judd, William
    - Ingersoll, Mary E. (Temperance worker, salary) - $6,096.00, 1888-1903 (Box 4, Folder 729)
    - Ingersoll, Miss M. E. (presents) - $300.00, 1885-1891 (Box 4, Folder 730)
    - Ingersoll, Rev. E. P. - $200.00, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 731)
      Miss Tuttle (through)
    - Ingersoll, Rev. Wilber M. - $200.00, 1888-1890 (Box 4, Folder 732)
    - International Medical Missionary Association (New York) - $3,410.00, 1886-1898 (Box 4, Folder 733)
      Dorknott, George D.
    - Invalids Home (Cleveland, Ohio) - $200.00, 1887-1893 (Box 4, Folder 734)
      Miss Spelman; White, Mrs. J. S.
    - Iowa Church - $108.00, 1863-1878 (Box 4, Folder 735)
    - Irish Baptist Churches (Ireland) - $7,521.86, 1892-1893 (Box 4, Folder 736)
      Drummond, W. H.
    - Irvine, T. M. (poor man) - $15.00, 1888 (Box 4, Folder 737)
    - Italian Hospital - $50.00, 1891 (Box 4, Folder 738)
      Mme. Giovannini
    - Ithaca, New York Baptist Church - $12,000.00, 1890-1891 (Box 4, Folder 739)
      Jones, Rev. Robert T.
    - Ives, W. J. (his Sunday School class) - $50.00, 1883 (Box 4, Folder 740)
    - Mrs. Jackson - $25.00, 1895 (Box 4, Folder 741)
    - Jackson, Rev. Alex - $100.00, 1902 (Box 4, Folder 742)
      Osborn, A. T.
    - Jamestown, New York Baptist Church - $1,000.00, 1890-1892 (Box 4, Folder 743)
      Preston, Jerome
    - Japan Church Bell - $10.00, 1887 (Box 4, Folder 744)
    - Jerome, William Travers - $4,000.00, 1901 (Box 4, Folder 745)
      Murphy, S. J. (anonymous for political fund)
    - Jewett, Evalyn (education children) - $1,050.00, 1887-1902 (Box 5, Folder 746)
    - Johns, Stacy - $1,100.00, 1892-1898 (Box 5, Folder 747)
      Johns, Mary D.
    - Mrs. Johnson (rent) - $220.00, 1882-1889 (Box 5, Folder 748)
    - Johnson, Guy B. - $620.00, 1883-1889 (Box 5, Folder 749)
    - Johnson, Almira (music) - $20.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 750)
    - Johnson, Helen - $145.00, 1889-1890 (Box 5, Folder 751)
    - Johnson, Wilhelmina - $20.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 752)
    - Johnson, Mrs. Isabella - $100.00, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 753)
    - Johnson, Rev. G. J. - $400.00, 1883-1885 (Box 5, Folder 754)
      Rev. Mr. Bickel; Dr. Huggins (for)
    - Johnson, Rev. R. P. - $800.00, 1901-1902 (Box 5, Folder 755)
    - Johnstown Relief Fund - $560.00, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 756)
    - Jones Home for Friendless Children (Cleveland, Ohio) - $4,075.00, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 757)
      Jones, J. D.
    - Jones School for Children - $50.00, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 758)
      Jones, C. L.
    - Jones, Chaplain J. D. - $250.00, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 759)
    - Josephine Mission - $10,210.00, 1883-1896 (Box 5, Folder 760)
      Miss Etzensperger; Rudd, W. C.; Smith, W. T.; Thomas, Ezra; Urquhart, William; Miss Waller
    - Mrs. Joslyn - $825.00, 1889-1895 (Box 5, Folder 761)
    - Judson, Rev. Edward (personal use)b - $6,820.00, 1882-1903 (Box 5, Folder 762)
    - Judson Memorial Church - $38,000.00, 1888-1891 (Box 5, Folder 763)
      Judson, Rev. Edward; Murray, George Wellwood
    - Judson Mission Society (Euclid Avenue Baptist Church, Cleveland, Ohio) - $35.00, 1884-1890 (Box 5, Folder 764)
    - Kane, Dr. Evan O'Neil (hospital work) - $1,000.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 765)
    - Rev. Mr. Kaufman (his salary) - $575.00, 1878-1886 (Box 5, Folder 766)
    - Mrs. Keffer - $75.00, 1891-1893 (Box 5, Folder 767)
    - Keith, Mrs. Kate S. - $25.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 768)
    - Keller, Helen - $900.00, 1896-1899 (Box 5, Folder 769)
      Greer, Rev. David Warner; Warner, Charles Dudley
    - Kendrick, Mrs. Georgia A. (memorial to Mr. Dean) - $50.00, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 770)
    - Kent House (Furnace and setting) - $72.90, 1874 (Box 5, Folder 771)
    - Kenton, Ohio Baptist Church - $250.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 772)
    - King, Albert Lester (concert) - $20.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 773)
    - King, Rev. C. D. - $100.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 774)
    - King, Rev. G. O. (personal use) - $1,174.53, 1881-1891 (Box 5, Folder 775)
    - King, Rev. G. O. (poor woman) - $50.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 776)
    - Mr. Kirkorian (missionary) - $100.00, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 777)
      Hansell, George H.
    - Kirtland, Ohio Baptist Church - $100.00, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 778)
      Buel, Rev. A. P.
    - Kitchen, H. W. (Central Committee) - $250.00, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 779)
    - Miss Kite - $700.00, 1891-1902 (Box 5, Folder 780)
      Barnes, Mrs. F. J.
    - Knight, Rev. William - $100.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 781)
    - Kohler, Rev. W. H. - $50.00, 1890-1891 (Box 5, Folder 782)
      Crandall, Rev. L. A.; Morehouse, Rev. H. L.
    - Kuchner, Camill - $50.00, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 783)
    - Kuppe, C. - $10.00, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 784)
    - Lacey, A. Eliza - $450.00, 1883-1903 (Box 5, Folder 785)
    - Mr. and Mrs. Ladd - $100.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 786)
    - Ladies Christian Union (New York City) - $7,000.00, 1894-1897 (Box 5, Folder 787)
      Cauldwell, Mrs. W. A.
    - Ladies International College Italy - $300.00, 1884-1885 (Box 5, Folder 788)
      Clark, William; Keith, F. C.
    - Ladies Musical Association (Cleveland, Ohio) - $1,250.00, 1886-1890 (Box 5, Folder 789)
      Crowell, Mrs. William; Harvey, Mrs. H. A.
    - Laird, Mrs. J. H. - $400.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 790)
    - Lake Erie Seminary - $10,600.00, 1891-1903 (Box 5, Folder 791)
      Burton, Miss E.; Child, C. O. (treas.); Gray, S. K.
    - Lake View congregational Church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $1,450.00, 1890-1902 (Box 5, Folder 792)
      Cowles, J. G. W.; Cristy, Mrs. A. B.; Miss Hanks; Ladd, Henry M.; Miss Wilburn
    - Lake Wood Baptist Church - $4,490.00, 1896-1903 (Box 5, Folder 793)
      Fielder, Mrs. M. E.; Smith, G. G.; Rev. Wedemeyer
    - Lakeside Hospital (Cleveland, Ohio) - $4,722.10, 1894-1900 (Box 5, Folder 794)
      Garfield, H. A. (treas.) (Samuel Mather); Kline, Mrs. V. P.
    - Lakeview Cemetery (Cleveland, Ohio) - $23,015.00, 1899-1903 (Box 5, Folder 795)
      Green, F.; Hatch, H. R.
    - LaMont, Mrs. Rachel - $500.00, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 796)
      Contribution in her name to First Baptist Church of Williamsport, Pennsylvania.
    - Lamonte, Lilian - $1,182.73, 1885-1900 (Box 5, Folder 797)
    - Lapham, J. H. - $50.00, 1881 (Box 5, Folder 798)
    - Lapin, Michigan Baptist Church (Box 5, Folder 799)
      (no entry on card)
    - Law and Order Association (Cleveland, Ohio) - $130.00, 1882-1886 (Box 5, Folder 800)
      Walton, J. W.
    - Law, Rev. S. G. - $75.00, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 801)
    - Miss Lawson - $175.00, 1890-1895 (Box 5, Folder 802)
    - Lawson, Rev. A. G. - $10.50, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 803)
    - Lawson, L. M. - $1,250.00, 1893-1894 (Box 5, Folder 804)
    - General Lawton (fund for widow) - $1,000.00, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 805)
      Root, Elihu
    - League for Social Service - $550.00, 1899-1900 (Box 5, Folder 806)
      Talman, W. H.; Trask, Spencer (treas.)
    - Leary, Charles - $250.00, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 807)
      Scheide, C. E.
    - Leavenworth Church, Kansas - $8.00, 1864-1865 (Box 5, Folder 808)
    - Leavitt, John W. - $75.00, 1890-1891 (Box 5, Folder 809)
    - Legal Aid Society - $700.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 810)
      Macy, V. E.
    - Leggett, Mrs. Gene - $200.00, 1896-1897 (Box 5, Folder 811)
    - Leonard, Rev. G. E. - $550.00, 1895-1897 (Box 5, Folder 812)
    - Lepper, Mrs. C. W. (her church) - $75.00, 1883, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 813)
    - Dr. LeRanger (Cleveland, Ohio) - $10.00, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 814)
    - Lewis, Mrs. J. B. - $200.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 815)
    - Lexington Avenue Baptist Church (New York) - $175.00, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 816)
      Braun, Aug
    - Lexington Colored Church - $20.00, 1865 (Box 5, Folder 817)
    - Lexow Committee - $1,000.00, 1894-1895 (Box 5, Folder 818)
      Orr, Alex E.
    - Lincolntown Baptist Church - $1.00, 1863 (Box 5, Folder 819)
    - Lisbon, Dakota Baptist Church - $250.00, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 820)
      Allen, Mrs. F. S.
    - Little Church (New York) - $50.00, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 821)
      Armitage, Rev. Thomas
    - Livermore, Mrs. J. M. - $50.00, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 822)
    - Livermore Baptist Church (Livermore, Iowa) - $75.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 823)
    - Loan Relief - $5.00, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 824)
      Avery, S. P. Jr.
    - Mrs. Gen. Logan - $1,000.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 825)
      Lemon, George E.
    - Logan Avenue Baptist Church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $11,175.00, 1884-1888 (Box 5, Folder 826)
      King, Rev. G. O.; Hyde, G. A.; Mrs. Robinson; Seaman, H. G.; Taylor, W. D.; Thomas, Ezra
    - Long, Rev. E. C. - $50.00, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 827)
    - Long Island Baptist Church - $500.00, 1889 (Box 5, Folder 828)
      Randall, N. B.
    - Lonsdale, J. F. (Bayonne) - $33.00, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 829)
    - Lorain, Ohio Baptist Church - $600.00, 1883 (Box 5, Folder 830)
      Hoyt, J. M.
    - Louisville Church - $150.00, 1879 (Box 5, Folder 831)
    - Lyon, Mrs. W. E. - $2,917.00, 1887-1902 (Box 5, Folder 832)
    - Mabie, Rev. H. C. - $100.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 833)
    - MacArthur, Rev. R. S. - $625.00, 1885-1890 (Box 5, Folder 834)
      Welch, Mrs. P. H.
    - Mace, Henry - $100.00, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 835)
    - Mackey, J. R. - $25.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 836)
    - Macy, Mrs. John H. (for poor woman) - $25.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 837)
    - Madison Avenue Congregational Church (Cleveland, Ohio) - $300.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 838)
      Bower, A. B.
    - Madison Avenue Presbyterian Church (New York) - $850.00, 1894-1896 (Box 5, Folder 839)
      Meigs, Mrs. T. B.; Stratton, A. B.
    - Madison, Indiana Baptist Church - $50.00, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 840)
      Dobbs, C. E. W.
    - Mann, Mrs. Edgar - $25.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 841)
      Van Liew, Henry P.
    - Mansfield, Mrs. H. - $50.00, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 842)
    - Marathon, New York Baptist Church - $100.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 843)
      Todd, Rev. A. H.
    - Marcy Avenue Baptist Church - $16,000.00, 1888-1899 (Box 5, Folder 844)
      Hills, John; Hudnot, Joseph
    - Margaret Stracham House - $233.74, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 845)
      Walsh, A. J. (for repairs)
    - Mariners Family Asylum - $300.00, 1887-1892 (Box 5, Folder 846)
      Jackson, Mrs. H. B.; MacDonald, Mrs. Frances
    - Mariners Temple, New York - $256.00, 1890, 1898 (Box 5, Folder 847)
      See also Avery, J. F.
    - Marion College Institute - $100.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 848)
      Colgrove, F. W.
    - Martin, Zerelda - $50.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 849)
    - Masonic Widows and Orphans (Memphis, Tennesee) - $50.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 850)
      Moulton, May Wheeler
    - McAll Mission (Paris, France) - $310.00, 1884-1892 (Box 5, Folder 851)
      Chisholm, Mrs. Wilson; Riley, Mrs. H. A.; Russell, Miss G. E.; Wood, Mrs. George
    - McAuley Cremorne Mission - $1,400.00, 1884-1902 (Box 5, Folder 852)
      Ballou, Charles E.; Jesup, C. M.
    - McAuley Mission (Water Street Mission) - $2,800.00, 1884-1902 (Box 5, Folder 853)
      Cutting, R. Fulton; Hadley, S. H.
    - McBride, Mrs. S. - $500.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 854)
      Dr. McBride (for)
    - McCabe, C. C. - $100.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 855)
    - Mcconn, Frank - $10.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 856)
    - McCormick, H. F. - $100.00, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 857)
    - McCormick, Harold F. - $100.00, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 858)
    - McDonald, Mrs. Celestia - $150.00, 1891-1894 (Box 5, Folder 859)
    - McKinley Memorial Association - $1,000.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 860)
      Cannon, J. G.
    - McKinstry, Mrs. A. M. - $208.00, 1895-1897 (Box 5, Folder 861)
      Miss Butler (to aid); Mrs. Middlebrook (to aid); Mrs. Taylor
    - McLean, Alex - $175.50, 1894-1896 (Box 5, Folder 862)
      Sutherland, Mrs. M. J.
    - McPheleny, Jno. - $10.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 863)
    - Medina, Ohio Baptist Church - $50.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 864)
    - Mellen, L. F. - $50.00, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 865)
    - Memorial Arch Washington Square - $500.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 866)
      Stewart, William R.
    - Memorial Baptist Church - $2,500.00, 1902-1903 (Box 5, Folder 867)
      Judson, Rev. E.
      See also Berean Baptist Church.
    - Memphis Baptist Bible and Training School - $100.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 868)
      Countee, Rev. R. N.
    - Merchants Association (New York) - $1,500.00, 1900-1901 (Box 5, Folder 869)
      Webb, C. H.
    - Merick, Hattie A. (Salary as missionary, Trinity Baptist Church, New York) - $315.00, 1883-1884 (Box 5, Folder 870)
    - Methodist Church Mountain Inn - $100.00, 1895-1896 (Box 5, Folder 871)
      Gill, Rev. John; St. Hill, C. J.
    - Metropolitan Museum (New York) - $500.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 872)
      Morgan, J. Pierpont
    - Mr. Middleton (for Methodist Episcopal church) - $22.00, 1890 (Box 5, Folder 873)
    - Miles City, Montana Baptist Church - $200.00, 1882-1883 (Box 5, Folder 874)
      Downey, George B.
    - Miles Testimonial Fund - $1,000.00, 1897 (Box 5, Folder 875)
      Tappan, Frederick D.
    - Milliken, David Jr. - $60.00, 1893-1902 (Box 5, Folder 876)
    - Milwaukee Baptist Church - $2,000.00, 1883-1891 (Box 5, Folder 877)
      Deitz, Rev. H. L.; Hurlburt, Rev. D. W.
    - Minnesota Baptist State Convention - $8,499.96, 1895-1903 (Box 5, Folder 878)
      Pope, Rev. E. R.; Ridgeway, J. A. (treas.)
    - Minnesota Conference Evangelical Lutheran Synod - $700.00, 1900-1901 (Box 5, Folder 879)
      Krantz, Rev. J. A. (through)
    - Minnesota Congregational Church Work - $2,400.00, 1897-1901 (Box 5, Folder 880)
      Merrill, George R. (supt.); Morley, Rev. J. H.
    - Minnesota Episcopal Church (missionary work) - $1,400.00, 1895-1897 (Box 5, Folder 881)
      Ames, J. H.
    - Minnesota Methodist Church Work - $3,000.00, 1896-1898 (Box 5, Folder 882)
      Fowler, Rev. C. H.
    - Minnesota Presbyterian Church - $2,000.00, 1898-1901 (Box 5, Folder 883)
      Adams, Rev. R. N.
    - Minton, Robert (to defeat Isaac H. Maynard) - $100.00, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 884)
    - Missionary to China - $10.00, 1863 (Box 5, Folder 885)
    - Missionary to Koreans - Mrs. Vinton - $10.00, 1863 (Box 5, Folder 886)
      Through Erie Street Baptist Church
    - Mitchell, Dr. Weir (for his work) - $8,500.00, 1894-1903 (Box 5, Folder 887)
      Mrs. Strong
    - Mrs. Mitchell - $27.63, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 888)
    - Miss Mittleburger (present to the school) - $150.00, 1882 (Box 5, Folder 889)
    - Mollenhauser, Grace W. - $50.00, 1896 (Box 5, Folder 890)
    - Monclair Baptist Church - $700.00, 1890-1892 (Box 5, Folder 891)
      Babcock, Paul Jr.; Cary, E. V.
    - Monkman, F. - $330.00, 1866-1901 (Box 5, Folder 892)
    - Monkman, Tillie - $50.00, 1892-1894 (Box 5, Folder 893)
    - Montefiore Home - $150.00, 1896-1898 (Box 5, Folder 894)
      Bonheur, L. L.
    - Montreal Baptist Church (collection) - $7.00, 1892 (Box 5, Folder 895)
    - Moody, Rev. D. L. - $32,620.00, 1890-1899 (Box 5, Folder 896)
      Moore, H. M.; Revel, F. H.; Talcott, J. F.
    - Moody, Rev. W. R. (Work at Northfield) - $20,000.00, 1900-1902 (Box 5, Folder 897)
    - Moore, Mrs. C. S. - $1,853.00, 1886-1902 (Box 5, Folder 898)
    - Moore, E. H. - $80.53, 1901 (Box 5, Folder 899)
    - Morgan, Charles - $225.00, 1885-1887 (Box 5, Folder 900)
    - Mormon Bible - $100.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 901)
      Middleditch, Livingston
    - Mr. Morney - $35.00, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 902)
    - Morris, H. J. - $31.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 903)
    - Morris, Mrs. William - $110.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 904)
    - Morristown Baptist Church - $500.00, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 905)
      Cauldwell, Thomas W.
    - Morse, Rev. F. R. - $550.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 906)
    - Mosier, Rev. W. J. - $100.00, 1887-1888 (Box 5, Folder 907)
    - Mount Holyoke Seminary - $54,014.58, 1887-1898 (Box 5, Folder 908)
      Williston, A. L.
    - Mount Morris Baptist Church (New York) - $4,000.00, 1887 (Box 5, Folder 909)
      Bitting, Rev. W. C.
    - Mount Olivet Baptist Church - $11,016.01, 1884-1902 (Box 5, Folder 910)
      Barnes, H. F.; Comey, J. L.
    - Mount Vernon, Illinois Baptist Church - $200.00, 1888 (Box 5, Folder 911)
      Howard, Mrs. M.
    - Moxom, Rev. P. S. - $250.00, 1885 (Box 5, Folder 912)
    - Mrs. Muncie - $185.00, 1892-1894 (Box 5, Folder 913)
    - Munger, Mrs. Helen F. - $50.00, 1893 (Box 5, Folder 914)
    - Murphy, Rev. Francis - $100.00, 1903 (Box 5, Folder 915)
    - Murphy and Lloyd - $60.10, 1900 (Box 5, Folder 916)
      Investigation of various appeals in behalf of philanthropic institutions.
    - Murphy meetings in New York - $100.00, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 917)
      Hadley, H. H.
    - Music Hall (Cleveland, Ohio) - $5,000.00, 1886 (Box 5, Folder 918)
      Doan, W. H.
    - Music Hall Missionary (Cleveland, Ohio) - $400.00, 1887-1888 (Box 5, Folder 919)
      Johnson, Rev. William; Pattison, S. Louise
    - Muskogee, Indian Territory Baptist Church - $200.00, 1891 (Box 5, Folder 920)
      Crosby, Rev. D.
    - Mrs. Myers - $65.00, 1898-1899 (Box 5, Folder 921)
    - Myers, Elijah - $100.00, 1889-1890 (Box 5, Folder 922)
    - Naptha Launch for Missionary - $25.00, 1889 (Box 6, Folder 923)
    - National Anti-Saloon League - $7,500.00, 1899-1902 (Box 6, Folder 924)
      Russell, H. H.
    - National Civic Federation - $600.00, 1900-1901 (Box 6, Folder 925)
      Bigelow, E. A; Fairchild, C. S.
    - National Conference of Charities and Corrections - $200.00, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 926)
    - National Conservatory of Music - $1,100.00, 1894-1897 (Box 6, Folder 927)
    - National Federation of Churches - $2,000.00, 1900-1904 (Box 6, Folder 928)
      Hughes, Charles E.
    - National League for the Protection of American Institutions - $4,900.00, 1885-1899 (Box 6, Folder 929)
      Baker, Rev. George S. 1885-1896; King, J. M.; Morgan, W. Fellowes
    - National Prison Association - $100.00, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 930)
      Byers, A. G.
    - National Sound Money League - $2,000.00, 1897-1900 (Box 6, Folder 931)
      Hepburn, A. B.
    - National Temperance Society - $19,777.55, 1879-1902 (Box 6, Folder 932)
      Cuyler, Rev. T. L.; Foster, E. C.; Porter, William D.; Stearns, Rev. J. N.; Miss Willard
    - New Haven Baptist Church (church extension work) - $500.00, 1892 (Box 6, Folder 933)
      Curtiss, C. B.
    - New Jersey Baptist State Convention - $11,000.00, 1893-1903 (Box 6, Folder 934)
      Dewolf, Rev. D.
    - New Rochelle Methodist Church - $100.00, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 935)
      Siebrecht, H. A.
    - New Testament Institute - $100.00, 1884 (Box 6, Folder 936)
      Rhoades, W. C. P.
    - New York Association for Improving Condition of the Poor - $17,700.00, 1886-1903 (Box 6, Folder 937)
      Hansell, George H.; Minton, Robert Shaw; Van Nordon, Warner
    - New York Association of Sewing Schools - $25.00, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 938)
      Patterson, Miss J.
    - New York Baptist State Convention - $91,652.12, 1885-1903 (Box 6, Folder 939)
      Barnes, Rev. H. W.; Calvert, Rev. J. B.; Jones, T. R.
    - New York Baptist Young People's Union (Fresh Air Fund) - $95,177.86, 1891-1902 (Box 6, Folder 940)
      Conkling, W. B.; Crane, W. M.; Marsten, Edgar L.; Townsend, Charles P.; Willard, Charles E.
    - New York Botanical Garden - $26,000.00, 1895-1896 (Box 6, Folder 941)
      Morgan, J. P.; Vanderbilt, C.
    - New York City Mission - $100.00, 1890 (Box 6, Folder 942)
      Andrews, Constant A.
    - New York Civil Service Reform Association - $400.00, 1902-1903 (Box 6, Folder 943)
      Chamberlin, L. T.; Goodwin, E. H.
    - New York Cooking School (United Charities Building) - $10.00, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 944)
    - New York Day Nurseries - $50.00, 1890-1891 (Box 6, Folder 945)
      Nurburg, Mrs. I. S.
    - New York Diet Kitchen - $25.00, 1902 (Box 6, Folder 946)
      Freeman, Mrs. Julia B.
    - New York Driving Club - $50.00, 1888 (Box 6, Folder 947)
      DeCordova, Alfred
    - New York Ecumenical Conference on Foreign Missions in New York - $1,000.00, 1900 (Box 6, Folder 948)
      Murray, William D.
    - New York Exchange for Women's Work - $217.00, 1886-1899 (Box 6, Folder 949)
    - New York Federation of Churches - $1,200.00, 1896-1902 (Box 6, Folder 950)
      Bessing, John; Dill, A. C.; Fisk, Harvey Jr.; Rowe, W. H. Jr.
    - New York Free Circulating Library - $1,500.00, 1890, 1895 (Box 6, Folder 951)
      Fields, Benjamin H.; Schiff, Jacob H.
    - New York Free Library for Blind - $50.00, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 952)
      Williams, Clara A.
    - New York Genealogical and Biographical Society - $100.00, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 953)
      James, Thomas L.
    - New York Herald Ice Fund and World Sick Babies Fund - $52.00, 1894-1896 (Box 6, Folder 954)
      Mason, S. H.
    - New York Historical Society (life membership) - $100.00, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 955)
    - New York Home for Convalescents - $10.00, 1898 (Box 6, Folder 956)
      Bowland, Mrs. H. F.
    - New York Homeopathic Medical and Free Hospital - $26,350.00, 1887-1897 (Box 6, Folder 957)
      Allen, Dr. T. F.; Flower, R. P.
    - New York Kindergarten Association - $4,250.00, 1899-1902 (Box 6, Folder 958)
      Bruce, J. M; Locke, Bessie; Trusk, Spencer
    - New York Medical College and Hospital for Women (19 West 101st Street) - $1,325.00, 1885-1901 (Box 6, Folder 959)
      Boyd, Mrs. J. Gray; Day, Mrs. H. L.; Demorest, Mrs. E. L.; Robinson, Mrs. M. K.; Wilson, Mrs. L. E.
    - New York Opthalmic Hospital - $4,200.00, 1886-1902 (Box 6, Folder 960)
      Allen, Dr. T. F.; Benedict, E. C.; Houghton, Dr. H. C.
    - New York Port Society - $200.00, 1885-1888 (Box 6, Folder 961)
      Dodge, R. J.
    - New York Protestant Half Orphan Asylum - $50.00, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 962)
      Brewster, Mrs. B.
    - New York Relief Fund for Poor - $5,000.00, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 963)
      Mayor of New York
    - New York Society for Prevention of Cruelty to Children - $1,800.00, 1894-1902 (Box 6, Folder 964)
      Jenkins, E. Fellows; Pratt, Dallas B.
    - New York State Anti-Saloon League - $19,223.00, 1899-1903 (Box 6, Folder 965)
      Baldwin, T. H.; Clark, J. L.; Russell, H. H.; Teal, J. H.
    - New York State Charities Aid Association - $1,300.00, 1898-1909 (Box 6, Folder 966)
      Fairchild, Charles S.
    - New York Swedish Methodist Church - $100.00, 1891 (Box 6, Folder 967)
      Olson, Rev. H.
    - New York Symphony Society - $4,000.00, 1891-1893 (Box 6, Folder 968)
      Reno, Morris
    - New York Tribune (Fresh Air Fund) - $250.00, 1897 (Box 6, Folder 969)
      Sattig, J. H.
    - New York Zoological Society - $5,000.00, 1901 (Box 6, Folder 970)
      Barney, C. T.
    - Newark Baptist Church (New Jersey) - $25.00, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 971)
      Schenck, Rev. C.
    - Newark First Baptist Church - $750.00, 1888, 1893 (Box 6, Folder 972)
      Boyd, W. W.
    - News Boys Home (Cleveland, Ohio) - $12.00, 1878, 1882 (Box 6, Folder 973)